Guide to the Records of the American Institute of the City of New York for the Encouragement of Science and Invention 1808-1983 (bulk, 1828-1940) MS 17
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Annual Fair Years, 1808-1930
  - Subseries 3: Bound Volumes, 1828-1936, n.d.
    - [Account books] Receipts and Disbursements, 39th and 40th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 625, Volume 31)
    - [Account books] Cash Received at the 40th Annual Fair of the American Instutite, 1871 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 32)
    - [Account books] 1) The Estate of Frederick H. Wetmore in Account Current with William J. Hoppin and Charles W. Hull 2) James Y. Watkins in Account with the American Institute, 1871-8172; 1908-1911 (Offsite-box 639, Volume 33)
    - [Account books] Cash Received at the 41st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1872 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 34)
    - [Account books] Receipts and Disbursements, 41st through 44th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1872-1875 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 35)
    - [Account books] Ledger, 41st to 6st Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1872-1892 (Offsite-box 624, Volume 36)
    - [Account books] Admission Fees and Dues from Members, 1873 (Offsite-box 639, Volume 37)
    - [Account books] Admission Fees and Dues from Members, 1875 (Offsite-box 639, Volume 38)
    - [Account books] Statement Book -- Receipts and Disbursements, 1875-1888 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 39)
    - [Account books] Receipts and Disbursements, 45th through 48th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1876-1879 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 40)
    - [Account books] Cash Book of the American Institute, Edward Schell, Treasurer, 1879-1894 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 41)
    - [Account books] Memorandums -- Edward Schell's Treasurer's Accounts, 1880- 1882 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 42)
    - [Account books] Receipts and Disbursements, 49th through 55th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1880-1886 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 43)
    - [Account books] Memorandums -- Edward Schell's Treasurer's Accounts, 1882-1885 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 44)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger No. 3, 1884-1929 (Offsite-box 640, Volume 45)
    - [Account books] Memorandums -- Edward Schell's Treasurer's Accounts, 1885-1887 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 46)
    - [Account books] Memorandums -- Edward Schell's Treasurer's Accounts, 1887-1889 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 47)
    - [Account books] Receipts and Disbursements, 56th to 61st Annual Fairs, and 65th to 69th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1887-1892; 1896-1899 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 48)
    - [Account books] Statement Book -- Receipts and Disbursements, 1888-1892 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 49)
    - [Account books] Expense Account, 1889 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 50)
    - [Account books] Admission Fees and Dues, etc., 1889 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 51)
    - [Account books] Express Cartage and Freight, 58th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1889 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 52)
    - [Account books] Memorandums -- Edward Schell's Treasurer's Accounts, 1889-1891 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 53)
    - [Account books] Freight Express and Cartage Bank Account, 59th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1890 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 54)
    - [Account books] Statements, 1890 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 55)
    - [Account books] Admission Fees and Dues Expense Accounts, Fairs and A. I., 1890 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 56)
    - [Account books] Expense Account, Postage, etc., 1891 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 57)
    - [Account books] Admission Fees and Dues Bank Account, 1891 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 58)
    - [Account books] Memorandums -- Edward Schell's Treasurer's Accounts, 1891-1893 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 59)
    - [Account books] Expense Account, 1892 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 60)
    - [Account books] Express Freight and Cartage, 61st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1892 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 61)
    - [Account books] Admission Fees and Dues Bank Account, 1892 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 62)
    - [Account books] William Dean in Account with the American Institute, 1894-1896 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 63)
    - [Account books] List of Receipts and Expenditures of the 65th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1896 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 64)
    - [Account books] [Entry Fees], 65th and 66th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1896-1897 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 65)
    - [Account books] William Dean, Treasurer, in Account with the American Institute, 1896-1897 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 66)
    - [Account books] Cash Received for Space, 66th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1897 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 67)
    - [Account books] List of Receipts and Expenditures of the 66th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1897 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 68)
    - [Account books] W. H. Oakley in Account with the American Institute, 1897-1900 (Offsite-box 641, Volume 69)
    - [Account books] Journal, 1897-1912 (Offsite-box 642, Volume 70)
    - [Account books] List of Receipts and Expenditures of the 67th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1898 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 71)
    - [Account books] James Y. Watkins in Account with the American Institute, 1900-1902 (Offsite-box 642, Volume 72)
    - [Account books] Receipts and Disbursements, 72nd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1903 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 73)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1904 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 74)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1905 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 75)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1906 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 76)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1907 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 77)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1908 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 78)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1909 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 79)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1910 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 80)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1911 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 81)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1912 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 82)
    - [Account books] Journal, 1912-1924 (Offsite-box 642, Volume 83)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1913 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 84)
    - [Account books] Petty Cash Book, 1913-1920 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 85)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1914 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 86)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1915 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 87)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1916 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 88)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1917 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 89)
    - [Account books] Members' Ledger (in Hollinger box), 1918 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 90)
    - [Account books] Francis C. Elgar, Treasurer, in Account with the American Institute, 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 642, Volume 91)
    - [Account books] Journal, 1923-1930 (Offsite-box 642, Volume 92)
    - [Account books] Francis C. Elgar, Treasurer, in Account with the American Institute, 1924-1926 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 93)
    - [Account books] Statement Book -- Receipts and Disbursements, 1927 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 94)
    - [Account books] Petty Cash Book, 1931-1936 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 95)
    - [Account books] 1) American Institute in Account with Geo. Baron 2) List of Bills of the 7th through 11th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, n.d., 1834-1838 (Offsite-box 626, Volume 96)
    - [Bank books] American Institute in Account with Chemical Bank, 1831 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 97)
    - [Bank books] Mechanics' Banking Association in Account with the American Institute, 1855-1857 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 98)
    - [Bank books] Register of Premiums Awarded at the 31st Annual Fair of the American Institute -- Agricultural and Horticultural Dept., 1859 (Offsite-box 622, Volume 99)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with John W. Chambers, Secretary, Board of Managers of the American Institute, 1881-1892 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 100)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the Board of Managers of the 60th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1891 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 101)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the Board of Managers of the 61st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1892 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 102)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the American Institute, 1893, 1894, 1897 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 103)
    - [Bank books] Bank of the Metropolis in Account with George Whitefield Jr., 1894 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 104)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the Board of Managers of the 65th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1896 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 105)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the American Institute, W. H. Oakley, Treasurer, 1897 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 106)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the Board of Managers of the 66th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1897-1898 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 107)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the Board of Managers of the 67th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1898 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 108)
    - [Bank books] Fifth Avenue Trust Co. in Account with the American Institute, 1899 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 109)
    - [Bank books] The National Citizens' Bank in Account with the Board of Managers of the American Institute, 1899-1900 (Offsite-box 459, Volume 110)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1839-1845 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 111)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book from Members, 18th Annual fair of the American Institute (in Hollinger box), 1845 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 112)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book -- E. T. Backhouse, 1845-1846 (Offsite-box 460, Volume 113)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1845-1848 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 114)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1848-1856 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 115)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1856-1860 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 116)
    - [Cash books] Cash Collections, 1858-1869 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 117)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1860-1863 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 118)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1863-1868 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 119)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1868-1872 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 120)
    - [Cash books] Cash Collections, 1869-1873 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 121)
    - [Cash books] Cash Received at the 39th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1870 (Offsite-box 625, Volume 122)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1872-1879 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 123)
    - [Cash books] Cash Expenses, 1873 (Offsite-box 643, Volume 124)
    - [Cash books] Cash Collections, 1873-1886 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 125)
    - [Cash books] Cash Expenses, 1875-1877 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 126)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1879-1888 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 127)
    - [Cash books] Cash Receipts, 1885-1886 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 128)
    - [Cash books] Cash Collections, 1886-1918 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 129)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1888-1897 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 130)
    - [Cash books] Petty Cash Book, 1898-1904 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 131)
    - [Cash books] 1) Petty Cash Book 2) Roll Book, 1905-1907; n.d. (Offsite-box 644, Volume 132)
    - [Cash books] 1) Petty Cash Book 2) Estate of Frederick H. Whitmore in Account with Chas. Wager Hull, Executor (Connecticut Accounts), 1907-1913; 1872-1874 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 133)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book, 1911-1915 (Offsite-box 644, Volume 134)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book, 1915-1919 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 135)
    - [Cash books] Cash Collections, 1918-1922 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 136)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book: James Y. Watkins, Treasurer; Charles E. Schaffner, Treasurer, 1919-1922 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 137)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book, 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 138)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book, 1926-1928 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 139)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book, 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 140)
    - [Cash books] Cash Book, 1929-1931 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 141)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1852-1858 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 142)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1858-1859 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 143)
    - [Cash books] Receipts for Entry Fees, 38th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1870 (Volume 144)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 145)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1871-1872 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 146)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1873-1875 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 147)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1879 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 148)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1880-1881 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 149)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1883-1884 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 150)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1885 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 151)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1890 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 152)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1906-1907 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 153)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1910-1912 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 154)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1912-1914 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 155)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1914-1916 (Offsite-box 646, Volume 156)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1916-1919 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 157)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1919-1922 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 158)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1922-1924 (Volume 159)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1926-1927 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 160)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 161)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1929 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 162)
    - [Cash books] Check Stubs, 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 647, Volume 163)
    - [Cash books] Time Book (Payroll Book), 1884-1886 (Offsite-box 645, Volume 164)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 11th and 12th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1838-1839 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 165)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Finance Committee of the American Institute, 1839 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 166)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Agricultural Committee of the American Institute, 1839-1846 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 167)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Corresponding Committee of the American Institute, 1839-1848 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 168)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Printing and Publication Committee of the13th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1840 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 169)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 13th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1840 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 170)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committees of the 13th and 14th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1840-1841 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 171)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Committee on Manufactures of the American Institute, 1840-1841 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 172)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Executive Committee of the 13th and 14th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1840-1841 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 173)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Finance Committee of the 13th, 14th and 15th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1840-1842 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 174)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Committee of Arrangements of the13th, 14th, 15th and 16th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1840-1843 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 175)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 14th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1841 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 176)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committees of the 15th and 16th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1842-1843 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 177)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 16th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1843 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 178)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Committee of Arts and Sciences of the American Institute, 1843-1859 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 179)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Committee of Arrangements of the 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1844 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 180)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1844 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 181)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1844 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 265)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 17th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1844 (Offsite-box 616, Volume 266)
      Scope and Contents Note
      This appears to be a second, incomplete copy of the above minutes.
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Day, 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1845 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 182)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 18th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1845 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 183)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 18th and 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1845-1846 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 184)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Finance Committee of the 19th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1846 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 185)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 20th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1847 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 186)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 20th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1847 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 187)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Agricultural Committee of the American Institute, 1847-1853 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 188)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 21st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1848 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 189)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 21st and 22nd Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1848-1849 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 190)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Committee of Arrangements of the 22th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1849 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 191)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Printing and Publication Committee of the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1850 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 192)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Invitation Committee of the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1850 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 193)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 23rd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1850 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 194)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 23rd and 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1850-1851 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 195)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Finance Committee of the American Institute, 1850-1865 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 196)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Library Committee of the American Institute, 1850-1873 (Offsite-box 631, Volume 197)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Invitation Committee of the 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1851 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 198)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 24th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1851 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 199)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Printing and Publication Committee of the24th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1851-1852 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 200)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Finance Committee of the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1852 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 201)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Invitation Committee of the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1852 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 202)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 25th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1852 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 203)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 25th and 26th Annual Fairs of the American Institute, 1852-1853 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 204)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Interchange Committee of the American Institute, 1853 (Offsite-box 632, Volume 205)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Premium Committee of the 26th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1853 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 206)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Agricultural Committee of the American Institute, 1853-1859 (Offsite-box 632, Volume 207)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 208)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Ticket Committee of the 27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 209)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Printing and Publication Committee of the27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 210)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Finance Committee of the 27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 211)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Flag Committee of the 27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 212)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Committee on Gas, Light and Water of the27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 213)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Floor Committee No. 5. Viz: Agricultural and Horticultural Implements and Machinery and Carriages, Sleighs and Axles. 27th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1855 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 214)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 28th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1856 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 215)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 29th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1857 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 216)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 30th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1858 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 217)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 31st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1859 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 218)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the American Institute Committee of Manufactures, Science, and Art, 1860-1861 (Offsite-box 632, Volume 219)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 32nd, 33rd and 34th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1860-1862 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 220)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 35th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1863 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 221)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 36th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1864 (Offsite-box 648, Volume 222)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Finance Committee of the American Institute, 1865-1880 (Offsite-box 632, Volume 223)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 38th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1869 (Offsite-box 611, Volume 224)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 39th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1870 (Offsite-box 611, Volume 225)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 40th Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1871 (Offsite-box 611, Volume 226)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Committee on Audit of the 41st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1872 (Offsite-box 615, Volume 227)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 41st Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1872 (Offsite-box 611, Volume 228)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 42nd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1873 (Offsite-box 612, Volume 229)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Library Committee of the American Institute, 1873-1876 (Offsite-box 632, Volume 230)
    - [Minute books] Minutes of the Board of Managers of the 43rd Annual Fair of the American Institute, 1874 (Offsite-box 612, Volume 231)